[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "Which of the following is true?",
    "options": [
      "Human memory involves the ability to only preserve information",
      "Human memory involves the ability to only recover information",
      "Human memory involves the ability to neither preserve not recover information",
      "Human memory involves the ability to both preserve and recover information"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 3
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "__________ refers to connections between the nerve cells",
    "options": [
      "Storage",
      "Synapses",
      "Neuron",
      "Blood"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "In order to create a new memory, information must be changed into",
    "options": [
      "a usable form",
      "a long form",
      "a short form",
      "a visual form"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 0
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "The memory __________ process allows us to bring stored memories into conscious awareness.",
    "options": [
      "storage",
      "retrieval",
      "encoding",
      "forgetting"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "Which of the following is not a major domain of cognition?",
    "options": [
      "Judgment",
      "Attention",
      "Aggression",
      "Intelligence"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 2
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "Which of the following is not an assumption of the information processing view?",
    "options": [
      "Information is processed in steps or stages",
      "There are limits on how much information can be processed",
      "The human information processing system is interactive",
      "Information processing is analogous to computer processing"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "__________ refers to rote rehearsal of repetition",
    "options": [
      "elaborative rehearsal",
      "maintenance rehearsal",
      "meaningful rehearsal",
      "none of the above"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "__________ presentations can enhance working memory capacity",
    "options": [
      "multimodal",
      "unimodal",
      "one by one",
      "antimodal"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 0
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "Episodic and semantic memories are categorized under __________ memory",
    "options": [
      "procedural",
      "structural",
      "phonemic",
      "declarative"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 3
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "According to the neural network model, memory capacity depends on",
    "options": [
      "complexity of the synapses",
      "sparseness of representations",
      "spatial and temporal correlations between memories",
      "all of the above"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 3
  }
]